# Joe Rogers

Site Reliability Engineer Manager | AI Champion | Infrastructure Optimization 310.903.8312 | joerawr@gmail.com | linkedin:go2joerogers | Torrance, CA

### **Summary**

Over 5 years of Cloud transformation and optimization experience in SRE and DevOps. Four years managing a dynamic team of SREs to transform CICD deployments from vms to containers with an IaC first mindset. Al Champion empowering team members to 10x their performance. 15+ years of enthusiastic digital transformation.

#### Skills

Mentoring, Training, Motivating, EKS, Kubernetes, ECS, Fargate, Docker, IAM, VPC, Route 53, Bedrock, VSCode, Python, Bash, Copilot, Cloudflare, Datadog, Splunk, Terraform, Ansible Loves: Gemini, Claude, Perplexity, DeepSeek, Cline, Windsurf, OpenAI

## **Experience**

#### **Core Digital Media**

Playa Vista, CA

#### Site Reliability Engineer Manager

July 2021 - Present

- Led containerization project to modernize 50+ apps from EC2 to ECS
- Created internal Infrastructure LLM Slack Bot, championed AI code assistant tools, LLM adoption
- Instilled a mindset of Infrastructure as Code first principals, deploying infra that is repeatable, accountable, and managed via a single source of truth
- Migrated CI/CD from AWS Code Pipeline to GitLab CI, shifting left on testing, and cutting new app creation from two weeks to two days, and release lead time from one day to one hour.

#### **Core Digital Media**

Playa Vista, CA

#### **Principal System Administrator**

Jan 2019 - July 2021

- Migrated 500+ datacenter hosted VMWare VMs to AWS EC2
- Dramatically reduced our AWS costs
- Greatly increased code deployment from once a week to once a day by migrating from Jenkins to AWS Code Pipeline / Code Build / Code Deploy

**Lowermybills** Playa Vista, CA

**Senior System Engineer** 

Jan 2013 - Dec 2018

- Complete data center migration from one colo to another
- Migration to VMWare and 1000+ VMs
- Automation, Ansible, Puppet and Puppet

## **Education**

UCLA, Los Angeles

**Electrical Engineering**